Guide to the Lavoisier Manuscripts and Graphics Collection, circa 1750-1834 (bulk)
Lavoisier Manuscripts and Graphics Collection, circa 1750-1834 (bulk)
- Series XII. Cesar Francois Cassini's Cartes de France
  - Cassini Maps 1-20 (Box 32)
  - Cassini Maps 21-40 (Box 33)
  - Cassini Maps 41-60 (Box 34)
  - Cassini Maps 61-80 (Box 35)
  - Cassini Maps 81-100 (Box 36)
  - Cassini Maps 101-120 (Box 37)
  - Cassini Maps 121-140 (Box 38)
  - Cassini Maps 141-160 (Box 39)
  - Cassini Maps 161-181 (Box 40)